{"test_questions": [[{"question": "The format used to present the logic output for the various combinations of logic inputs to a gate is called a(n):", "opta": "truth table.", "optb": "input logic function.", "optc": "Boolean constant.", "optd": "Boolean variable.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the basic difference between AHDL and VHDL?", "opta": "ADHL is used in all PLD's.", "optb": "VHDL is used in all PLD's.", "optc": "ADHL is proprietary.", "optd": "VHDL is proprietary.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A small circle on the output of a logic gate is used to represent the:", "opta": "Comparator operation.", "optb": "OR operation.", "optc": "NOT operation.", "optd": "AND operation.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "For a three-input OR gate, with the input waveforms as shown below, which output waveform is correct?", "opta": "a", "optb": "b", "optc": "c", "optd": "d", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the figures given below represents a NOR gate?", "opta": "a", "optb": "b", "optc": "c", "optd": "d", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the figures (a to d) is the DeMorgan equivalent of Figure (e)?", "opta": "a", "optb": "b", "optc": "c", "optd": "d", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the figures in figure (a to d) is equivalent to figure (e)?", "opta": "a", "optb": "b", "optc": "c", "optd": "d", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In VHDL, the mode of a port does not define:", "opta": "an input.", "optb": "an output.", "optc": "both an input and an output.", "optd": "the TYPE of the bit.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following equations would accurately describe a 4-input OR gate when A = 1, B = 1, C = 0, and D = 0?", "opta": "1 + 1 + 0 + 0 = 1", "optb": "1 + 1 + 0 + 0 = 01", "optc": "1 + 1 + 0 + 0 = 0", "optd": "1 + 1 + 0 + 0 = 00", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the examples below expresses the distributive law?", "opta": "(A + B) + C = A + (B + C)", "optb": "A(B + C) = AB + AC", "optc": "A + (B + C) = AB + AC", "optd": "A(BC) = (AB) + C", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the examples below expresses the associative law of addition:", "opta": "A + (B + C) = (A + B) + C", "optb": "A + (B + C) = A + (BC)", "optc": "A(BC) = (AB) + C", "optd": "ABC = A + B + C", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How are the statements between BEGIN and END not evaluated in VHDL?", "opta": "Constantly", "optb": "Simultaneously", "optc": "Concurrently", "optd": "Sequentially", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which logic gate does this truth table describe?", "opta": "AND", "optb": "OR", "optc": "NAND", "optd": "NOR", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "For a 3-input NAND gate, with the input waveforms as shown below, which output waveform is correct?", "opta": "a", "optb": "b", "optc": "c", "optd": "d", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the figures given below represents a NAND gate?", "opta": "a", "optb": "b", "optc": "c", "optd": "d", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which timing diagram shown below is correct for an inverter?", "opta": "a", "optb": "b", "optc": "c", "optd": "d", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A NOR gate with one HIGH input and one LOW input:", "opta": "will output a HIGH", "optb": "functions as an AND", "optc": "will not function", "optd": "will output a LOW", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A NAND gate has:", "opta": "active-LOW inputs and an active-HIGH output.", "optb": "active-LOW inputs and an active-LOW output.", "optc": "active-HIGH inputs and an active-HIGH output.", "optd": "active-HIGH inputs and an active-LOW output.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the figures given below represents an OR gate?", "opta": "a", "optb": "b", "optc": "c", "optd": "d", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is a form of DeMorgan's theorem?", "opta": "", "optb": "", "optc": "", "optd": "", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The logic gate that will have HIGH or \"1\" at its output when any one of its inputs is HIGH is a(n):", "opta": "NOR gate", "optb": "OR gate", "optc": "AND gate", "optd": "NOT operation", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the symbols shown below represents an AND gate?", "opta": "a", "optb": "b", "optc": "c", "optd": "d", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "For a three-input AND gate, with the input waveforms as shown below, which output waveform is correct?", "opta": "a", "optb": "b", "optc": "c", "optd": "d", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An OR gate with inverted inputs functions as:", "opta": "an AND gate.", "optb": "a NAND gate.", "optc": "a NOR gate.", "optd": "an inverter.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The special software application that translates from HDL into a grid of 1's and 0's, which can be loaded into a PLD, is called a:", "opta": "formatter.", "optb": "compiler.", "optc": "programmable wiring.", "optd": "CPU.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The Boolean equation for a NOR function is:", "opta": "", "optb": "", "optc": "", "optd": "", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which step in this reduction process is using DeMorgan's theorem?", "opta": "STEP 1", "optb": "STEP 2", "optc": "STEP 3", "optd": "STEP 4", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Simplify the expression  using DeMorgan's theorems.", "opta": "", "optb": "", "optc": "", "optd": "", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "For a three-input NOR gate, with the input waveforms as shown below, which output waveform is correct?", "opta": "a", "optb": "b", "optc": "c", "optd": "d", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}